<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Assignment2</string>
    <string name= "team_dc">The Deccan Chargers, or Hyderabad Deccan Chargers known in short as DC, was a cricket franchise based in the city of Hyderabad in the Indian Premier League.[1] The team was one of the eight founding members of the IPL in 2008 and was owned by Deccan Chronicle Holdings Ltd. After finishing last in the first season of the IPL, they won the second season held in South Africa in 2009 under the captaincy of former Australian wicket-keeper and batsman Adam Gilchrist. Gilchrist was the captain of the team for the first three seasons of the IPL. From the fourth season, Kumar Sangakkara led the team and Cameron White played as his deputy. The team was coached by Darren Lehmann, former Australian cricketer.The owners put the franchise up for sale in 2012 but declined the sole bid. On 14 September 2012, the IPL governing council terminated the Chargers for breaching contract terms.[2] The Sun TV Network won the bid for the Hyderabad franchise, the BCCI conformed on 25 October 2012.[3] The new team was named the Sunrisers Hyderabad.[4]</string>
    <string name = "team_csk">The Chennai Super Kings (abbreviated as CSK) are a franchise cricket team based in Chennai, Tamil Nadu (India), which plays in the Indian Premier League (IPL). Founded in 2008, the team played its home matches at the M. A. Chidambaram Stadium in Chennai. On 14 July 2015, the Supreme Court appointed RM Lodha committee which suspended the Super Kings from the IPL for a period of two years for the alleged involvement of their owners in the 2013 Indian Premier League betting case.[2] Prior to the suspension, the team was captained by Mahendra Singh Dhoni and coached by Stephen Fleming. The Super Kings had won the title twice in succession (2010 and 2011).[3] In 2010, they won the Champions League Twenty20 for the first time and repeated the feat in 2014. They have played 8 Final in Total including CLT-20 and IPL.They have reached IPL playoffs each and every time. They held the record of most wins as a T20 Side till 2017 even after being banned for 2 years.They are regarded as the Best IPL Team of all. The leading run-scorer of the team is Suresh Raina, while the leading wicket-taker is Ravichandran Ashwin.[4][5] The brand value of the Super Kings in 2015 was estimated at $67 million, making them the third most valuable franchise in the IPL.</string>
    <string name = "team_rr">The Rajasthan Royals (often abbreviated as RR) is a cricket team in the Indian Premier League from the city of Jaipur, suspended till the 2017 season.[1] Founded in 2008 as one of the initial eight IPL franchises, the Royals are owned by Manoj Badale. The team played its home matches at the Sawai Mansingh Stadium in Jaipur and also had secondary home grounds at the Sardar Patel Stadium at Ahmedabad and the Brabourne Stadium at Mumbai. The Royals are sometimes considered the Moneyball team of the IPL.[2][3][4] The Royals are known to unearth obscure exciting talent.[5][6][7] The team won the inaugural edition of the IPL under the captaincy of Shane Warne, despite being written off as a title contender by the media and fans. The Royals were also the runners-up of the 2013 Champions League Twenty20 under Rahul Dravid\'s captaincy. On 14 July 2015 the verdict reached by a panel appointed by India\'s Supreme Court suspended Rajasthan Royals plus fellow Indian Premier League side Chennai Super Kings for two years over a corruption and match fixing scandal, meaning they could not participate in both the 2016 and 2017 IPL tournaments. Shane Watson is the only player to lead most runs,[9] most wickets,[10] highest score,[11] highest batting average,[12] most sixes,[13] for a team in T20. Also the only player to win man of the tournament in IPL twice.</string>
    <string name = "team_dd">The Delhi Daredevils (often abbreviated as DD) are a franchise cricket team representing the city of Delhi in the Indian Premier League (IPL). Founded in 2008 one of the eight founding teams of the IPL, the Delhi franchise is owned by the GMR Group. Their home grounds are the Feroz Shah Kotla Ground in Delhi and the Shaheed Veer Narayan Singh International Cricket Stadium in Chhattisgarh. qualified for Champions League T20 twice, making the Finals in the 2012 edition. However, in recent seasons, the team has strong attack, often ending up as wooden spooners. The team\'s current captain is Zaheer Khan while the coach and mentor are Paddy Upton and Rahul Dravid respectively. The leading run-scorer of the side is Virender Sehwag while the leading wicket-taker is Amit Mishra.</string>
    <string name="team_rcb">The Royal Challengers Bangalore (often abbreviated as RCB) are a franchise cricket team based in Bangalore, Karnataka, that plays in the Indian Premier League (IPL). One of the original eight teams in the IPL, the team has made three final appearances in the IPL, losing all of them (in 2009 to the Deccan Chargers, in 2011 to the Chennai Super Kings and in 2016 to the Sunrisers Hyderabad). The team also finished runners-up in the 2011 CLT20, losing the final against the Mumbai Indians. The home ground of the Royal Challengers is the M. Chinnaswamy Stadium in Bangalore.[1] The team is currently captained by Virat Kohli and coached by Daniel Vettori.[2][3] The team holds the records of both the highest and the lowest total in the IPL (263/5 and 49).</string>

</resources>
